It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marine Corps.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew
underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, they return to the Sabaody Archipelago
and move forward to the next stage of their journey,
the New World.
Am I mistaken, or did they call you Captain Luffy?
Why wouldn't they call me that?
I mean, you realize who you're talking to right now, don't you?
Go!
Get out of my way before I grab your intestines
and pull them out your ear!
Turn up, Starhack, you human pile of garbage!
You're not even close!
What?
So that's it.
They thought that they could join the Straw Hats
and enter the New World.
And although I cannot imagine why,
the real Straw Hat is here somewhere, too.
I was close!
It's... it's really him, isn't it?
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Second gear!
You're way too slow.
Gum gum jet testo!
This is worse than I thought.
He's able to use Aki now.
Luffy!
Shoulda known!
All I had to do was follow the explosions
and I knew I'd find you!
Man, it's been forever, huh?
I bet everyone's so cool now!
I can't wait to see!
I came to check on you,
but it seems you have this under control.
One last thing!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
Do you hear meeeeee?
Everyone together!
Luffy's setting out for the New World!
Things are getting ugly.
If they don't move quickly,
they won't make it out alive.
If they don't move quickly, they won't make it out alive.
What are you doing? Hurry up and capture them already!
Gotta move, Luffy! We appreciate the help, Rayleigh!
Well, we're off. Thanks again for everything. See ya! I'm outta here!
Good luck.
They're on the move! After them!
Let them get away!
Let nothing stop you from reaching the top!
They're on the move! After them!
Let them get away!
Let nothing stop you from reaching the top!
The Straw Hats are making a beeline for Grove 42!
Catch them at any cost!
Help!
It's our King Rayleigh!
Why don't you just let the boy sail?
He's been out of the game, so take it easy.
Let's get away!
Let nothing stop you from reaching the top!
The Straw Hats are making a beeline for Grove 42!
Catch them at any cost!
Help!
It's our King Rayleigh!
Take it easy!
That's an intense line!
If you think that's intense, then why don't you try crossing it?
Woah! That's a lot! You really went all out! What's inside?
It's our food stock!
I bought in bulk, cause I'm sure everyone's stomachs have gotten bigger over these two years!
This should keep us all happy for a while!
Good thinking! I haven't had your cooking in way too long!
Over here! We found them!
Crap, they get ahead of us somehow!
Looks like we're gonna have to fight our way through!
Charge in! We got this!
We got this!
I'm as worthless as a plea!
What's wrong?
Get up before-
Oh no!
What happened to their morale?
I'm nothing but a louse!
This sure looks familiar!
How did I know it was you guys causing that ruckus?
Huh?
So typical!
You're fooling around with the Navy when you should've been gone long ago!
Woah! Well, aren't you a sight for sore eyes!
Hey Miller!
Speak for yourself! If you were smart, you would've bailed by now!
You wouldn't even be here if it weren't for me, so don't start, mister!
Who knows where you would've wound up on your own!
The least you could do is be gracious!
She's an actual woman with real life girly parts!
Of course I am! What the hell is your damage, you freak?!
Alright, enough of this! You guys need to get moving!
There's Navy ships nearby, so you're running out of time!
If you don't get out of here soon, you'll never escape!
While that is bad, we have a bigger problem!
I can't seem to move from this spot at all!
Would you mind not being a total creepazoid?!
I can't help myself!
Take me!
I'm lower than earthworm poop!
Oh no!
What's that?
I finally found you guys!
Look who's here!
Usap!
Nami!
Rabban!
Rangki!
Oh right! You're here!
What a surprise! I didn't think you'd abandon stardom!
Attaboy!
Nothing could keep me from coming back! I've missed you all so!
I see that you two have only grown lovelier in our time apart!
With all that in mind, there's something I need to know!
Ooh! It's already song time, huh?
Please Nami, may I look at your panties?
No way in hell!
I never let you look at them two years ago, why would I let you see them now?
Right? I was just excited to see you!
It made my soul shake!
And it's still shaking right now!
In fact, it's about to leak out of my ear!
I-
I didn't think you could have a muscle spasm without any muscles!
Seriously?
How is it none of you have grown up after all this time?
Rejection aside,
I was actually expecting to be the last one here!
Don't worry, Chopper is off looking for our missing companion!
Huh?
Hey!
Oh!
Talk about perfect timing!
Guys!
Hey!
Told you I would find him!
Loopy!
Zoro!
Zatchi!
Hey!
Together again!
I've been waiting for this day!
And everyone looks stronger!
I like it!
It feels like it's been forever!
Looks like we're the last-
Hi guys!
Hey guys!
Huh?
Ah!
He's everything!
Thanks a lot for the ride!
Tell everyone back in the birdie kingdom I say hi!
How is he?
Has the bleeding stopped yet?
Not one, but two beautiful women in front of me!
Stay with me, man!
Don't give up yet!
It's no good, Chopper!
He's getting paler by the second!
You look so cool, Frankie!
Yeah, you think so?
Good!
But even if you didn't, I could change my style at will, Mecca!
Mecca!
Okay, focus!
This is no time to be fooling around!
We need to get out of here while we can before the Navy's on top of us!
He's on top of us!
No!
It looks like we're too late!
I see three Navy ships!
If we don't do something fast, we're gonna be dead in the water!
Fire!
Sink that ship at all costs!
Oh no!
They're gonna hit!
Mwah!
Slaaaaaaave!
No!
What?!
They're stopped in mid-air!
We...
Captain!
It's the Kuja Pirates!
Answer me this, Knaves!
Which one of you had the audacity to place your disgusting ship in my path?
No!
겠
steroikal
Mark
That flag.
It can't be.
You know it?
That's the Kuja Symbol.
They're a strong crew of Amazonian planes.
Amazonians led by one of the seven warlords.
You're joking, right?
Not at all. Her name is Boa Hancock.
They say anyone who lays eyes on her
will be enamored by her beauty and turned to stone,
unless she grants you mercy.
Whoa! Oh, I can see why.
Beauty starts and ends with her.
If I had eyes, they'd be sparkling.
Wow! She's a real-life goddess!
Is she really that fine?
Let me see!
My goddess, where?
Gotta find her. I wanna see.
I wanna, I wanna!
Ah! He's as hard as a rock!
Hancock said she wasn't coming here.
Huh?
We order you to move your ship out of the way!
You're interfering with official Navy business!
It's your ship that's in my way.
So I suppose it's you that's interfering
with official Navy business.
Uh, that's really an immature argument.
I get what I want.
Go, Luffy. I've bought you some time.
Oh!
Drinking us! I could die of ecstasy!
Looks like we have an opening.
Let's set sail!
Do you know that warlord or something?
Yeah. I made friends with her
when that bear guy sent me to Amazon Lily.
You mean the legendary island where only women live?
I never believed it was a real place.
You've been palling around with the pirate empress?
Come clean now!
You weren't really training at all
these past two years, were you?
What else would I have been doing?
Damn! It's not fair!
That would've been a dream come true!
What's his problem?
Wow!
So those are Luffy's friends.
I've never seen so many strange creatures together before.
There's one, two, three, four...
They look like such a fun crew!
Okay! Everyone in position to set sail!
Yes! There's one!
What's the matter, Usof?
Something just occurred to me.
You never said you beat the Navy soldiers inland.
We didn't.
We just flew past them,
but we could hear them shouting
from behind us in the distance.
Then what could be stopping them from coming after us?
This is Backup Unit Platoon 3!
Do you copy?
Me Reju, what's happening?
We are unable to reach Grove 42!
What? Why?
Well, because there are giant bugs
currently halting our advance!
Wait, giant what?
Ahh!
These things are monsters!
Shoot it!
Ahh!
I won't let anyone get in the way of Usofin going adventuring!
Men don't shed tears when they part ways!
Good luck, Usofin!
Ahh!
The worse their lives are, the better ours will be!
It's time to get out of here!
Nami!
Lead the way!
You got it!
Alright!
This is Platoon 4!
Afraid I have bad news!
All our gunpowder has been ruined by a sudden rain shower!
What?!
That is impossible!
The forecast for Sabaody Archipelago today is clear and sunny!
Thunder would be excessive!
After all, we don't want to scare the civilians now!
I wasn't expecting those bubbles to give us so much grief!
Bubbles or not, you can't complain about the wind!
No, sir!
That breeze got us where we wanted to be right on schedule!
Of course it did!
When it happened, it was the wind of the wind of the wind of the wind!
All our gunpowder has been ruined by a sudden rain shower!
What?!
That isn't possible!
Of course it did!
When it's something for Nami, she gets nothing but the best!
We'll miss you on Witharia, young lady!
But get out there and give it your all!
How are we doing this?
I'm getting slippery!
I'm getting too IF I want to think I need to act over two years of paradise!
No!
So nice!
Now that is what the hell has to do with me!
Hey, what's it doing?
Are you sure this is supposed to inflate?
Whoa! Now our boat's got a bubble roof!
This is how it works.
A ship that is properly coated has the ability to withstand almost any sort of pressure,
but it also has very little buoyancy.
The floating bag beneath the ship is the only thing keeping us afloat.
By deflating it, the sunning will become less buoyant and begin to sink.
It's pretty simple, really.
Oh, interesting.
Maybe not simple enough.
Forget about it for now. Let's spread the sail.
Why?
We use it to catch the water current, similar to how we would use the wind above sea level.
I was hoping we'd just sink down to Fishman Island. Darn.
All right! We'd better hurry unless we want to get in another fight!
This is Central Unit Platoon 5 at Grove 42.
We have an emergency!
The troops from Platoon 2 have been found, but they've all succumbed to a severe depression!
Tell him to suck it up and get back in the fight!
Come on!
I suck! I should have been born a waterfall!
What we've been able to gather is that straw hat Luffy flew off on a giant bird!
So he's not even there?
Then what are you guys shooting at?
We are currently under attack by unknown enemies!
What a jerk!
After all I've done for him, he's given me nothing but trouble!
I really should go find a new boy toy to play with.
Reinforcements got here quick!
We were just about to leave!
Heads up!
The straw hat ship is now within range!
But we may have a problem.
A large bird is heading straight for us!
Oh, wow!
From behind, too?
I got it!
You like what you see, Nami?
I've gotten a lot stronger.
Go ahead and take it in.
No, not again!
Platoon 5, come in!
What's going on?
Well, it isn't good.
We've hit interference.
We couldn't possibly have anticipated this.
Ah!
Have mercy!
How could you ever think of turning beauties like us away?
As if!
Maybe they're all shy.
There's nothing to be ashamed of, boys!
Let's have a cup of tea!
And cookies, too!
Oh, Waffle!
Truly, this is worse than death!
Hi there!
You've got such an adorable face!
No!
Let me go!
What's wrong now?
The 2-5 finish a report!
This is for you, Sanji.
Make it count.
Take it easy, Sanji.
Breathe!
Usopp, it's you.
Sorry, it felt like someone had gotten a death grip on my heart.
Bag's deflated!
Awesome.
You guys ready?
Yeah, we're all set.
That it, Nami?
Yeah.
Just say the word, Captain.
All right.
Listen up, guys!
There's a lot I want to say, but we don't have much time.
One thing can't wait, though.
What you went through these past two years was selfish of me, so thanks for putting up with it.
You make it sound like this has never happened before.
That's no joke.
You've always been a selfish piece of work.
Rear Admiral!
The pirate ship is submerging!
We can't wait!
Listen!
You have no idea how dangerous these pirates are!
Move your ship!
Now!
Pretty please!
Yes, please!
Take care of yourself, Luffy.
Luffy.
Spread the sail!
Right!
Let's go!
Yeah!
We're off to Fishman Island!
We go!
Encased in a protective bubble, the Sunny departs for Fishman Island far under the sea.
As the Straw Hats marvel at the sights, Frankie tells a tale of the man who proved to be the
crew's greatest ally in their time apart.
Then, suddenly, a mysterious shadow closes in on the ship.
On the next One Piece, a surprising fact, the man who guarded the Sunny.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!